

SKILLS

FRONT-END

JavaScript · TypeScript · React · C# · React Native · HTML · CSS · ES6

Back-End

NodeJS · Next JS

Database

 $\mathsf{MongoDB} \cdot \mathsf{Firebase}$

Tools and Libraries

Git · GitHub · ESLint · Jest · Axios ·

Tailwind CSS · Chakra UI · Ant Design ·

GSAP · Sass

SOFT SKILLS

Teamwork · Problem-solving ·

Communication

EDUCATION

Alpha JavaScript Track

Telerik Academy

01/2024 - 06/2024

Sofia, Bulgaria

Bachelor's degree, Accounting

VU7F

10/2009 - 07/2013

Sofia, Bulgaria

LANGUAGES

Bulgarian Native

English

Proficient

PASSIONS

- WEB DEVELOPMENT ENTHUSIAST
- ★ TAKING STROLLS IN NATURE
- BOARD GAMES WITH FRIENDS
- COMPETITIVE GAMING

RADOSLAV MARINOV

JavaScript Developer

- +359888788687 @ radoslav.marinov89@gmail.com
- Phttps://github.com/Radoslav-Marinovv

SUMMARY

With 1+ year of experience in frontend development and five completed projects, I am a graduate of the Telerik Academy's Alpha JS track. I have developed strong skills in frontend technologies, including HTML, CSS, JavaScript, TypeScript, and React, along with back-end knowledge in Node.js, Next.js, and Firebase. I am also well-versed in UI libraries such as Tailwind CSS, Ant Design, and Chakra UI.

I am eager to apply my diverse experience, creative thinking, and technical skills to contribute to the development of software projects and applications.

PROJECTS

Portfolio: Portfolio Hosted on Vercel

08/2024 - Present

This portfolio is built with Vite and React and is an ongoing project designed to showcase my skills and experience. It features smooth animations with GSAP and responsive design using Tailwind CSS. Through this platform, I aim to present my personal projects, technical abilities, and creativity.

- React.js, Type Script
- TailwindCSS, GSAP, Git

Fitness Tracking Application: Motion Mate

06/2024 - 06/2024

Fitness tracking application, where users can track their daily exercises, such as calories burned, exercises done, or other activities. Users can set their goals and track their progress. They can also add their friends and see their progress as well.

- · React.js, JavaScript, Firebase, Tailwind CSS
- · daisy UI, Git

Phttps://a58-agents-team1.github.io/Motion.Mate/

Forum: Tasty Recipe Talk

05/2024 - 05/2024

As part of a team, I was involved in creating the food recipe forum, creating the database connection, the GitHub repository. Building functionality and style of the project.

- React.js, JavaScript, Firebase
- Chakra Ul. Git

RELEVANT EXPERIENCE

Freelance Developer

02/2023 - 06/2023

Groshev & Partners

Sofia, Bulgaria

Led client communication to understand and refine project requirements, planned the optimal technologies for the project, and outlined the steps needed to meet the client's criteria.

- Next.js, React.js, Type Script, JSON
- Additional Libraries: TailwindCSS, Daisy UI, Google Blogger API

Frontend Developer

06/2022 - 12/2022

TECHSTORM LTD

Sofia, Bulgaria

Contributed to the development of an MVP website as a frontend developer and a mobile application. Enhanced existing functionality and implemented new features by efficiently completing assigned tasks.

- Tech stack: Next.js, React.js, React Native, Type Script, MongoDB, JSON.
- Additional Libraries: Auth0, Ant Design, Axios, Moment JS, TailwindCSS, React Router.